Lesson 50. New Year resolutions. The New Year is a time for resolutions. Mentally, at least,
第50课。新年决议。新的一年是决议的时候。至少在精神上，
compile: v.   编辑，编制, formidable: adj. 令人畏惧的
most of us could compile formidable lists of dose, and, don'ts. The same old favorites
我们大多数人都可以汇总强大的剂量列表，以及不做。同样的旧收藏夹
recur: v.   再发生，又出现, regularity: n.   规律性
recur year in year out with monotonous regularity. We resolve to get up earlier each morning.
单调规律性的年度重复。我们决心每天早晨起床。
Eat less. Find more time to play with the children. Do a thousand and one jobs about the house.
少吃。寻找更多时间与孩子们一起玩。为房子做一千和一项工作。
Be nice to people we don't, like. Drive carefully. And take the dog for a walk every day.
对我们不喜欢的人很好。小心地开车。每天带狗散步。
accomplishment: n.   成就, attainment: n.   达到
Past experience has taught us that certain accomplishments are beyond attainment. If we remain
过去的经验告诉我们，某些成就是无法实现的。如果我们留下来
in veteran smokers, it is only because we have so often experienced the frustration that results
在退伍军人吸烟者中，这仅仅是因为我们经常经常经历挫败感
self-improvement: n.   自我完善, scheme: n.   简单的计划，方案
from failure. Most of us fail in our efforts at self-improvement because our schemes are too
从失败。我们大多数人都在自我完善的努力中失败了，因为我们的方案也是
ambitious: adj. 雄心勃勃的
ambitious and we. Never have time to carry them out. We also make the fundamental error of
雄心勃勃，我们。永远没有时间执行它们。我们还犯了根本错误
announcing our resolutions to everybody so that we look even. More foolish when we slip back into
向所有人宣布我们的决议，以便我们看起来更加看。当我们溜回到
pitfall: n.   意外的困难，易犯的错误
our battled ways. Aware of these pitfalls, this year I attempted to keep my resolutions to myself.
我们的战斗方式。意识到这些陷阱，今年我试图将自己的决议保留给自己。
modest: adj. 要求不过分的
I limited myself to two modest ambitions. To do physical exercise every morning and to read more
我将自己限于两个谦虚的野心。每天早晨进行体育锻炼并阅读更多
of an evening. An all night party on New Year's Eve provided me with a good excuse for not
一个晚上。除夕的全夜聚会为我提供了一个很好的借口
carrying out either of. These new resolutions on the first day of the year. But on the second,
执行任何一个。这些新决议在一年中的第一天。但是第二
I applied myself acidwously to the task. The daily exercises lasted only 11 minutes and I
我将自己应用于任务。每日练习持续了11分钟，我
self-discipline: n.   自我约束
proposed to do them early in the morning. Before anyone had got up, the self-discipline required
建议在清晨做。在任何人起床之前，需要自律
to drag myself out of bed 11 minutes earlier than usual was. Considerable, nevertheless,
比平常早11分钟将自己拖出床。不过，尽管如此
I managed to creep down into the living room for two days before anyone found me out.
在任何人发现我之前，我设法爬进了客厅两天。
frame: n.   躯体
After jumping about on the carpet and twisting the human frame into uncomfortable positions,
在地毯上跳来跳去并将人框架扭曲成不舒服的位置之后，
betray: v.   暴露，显露
I sat down at the breakfast table in an exhausted condition. It was this that betrayed me.
我坐在早餐桌上，状况良好。就是这样背叛了我。
troop: v.   成群结队地走动
The next morning the whole family trooped in to watch the performance. That was really unsettling,
第二天早上，整个家庭都在观看表演。那真的很令人不安，
taunt: n.   嘲笑，奚落人的话, jibe: n.   嘲弄，挖苦
but I fended off the taunts and jibes of the family good humoredly and soon everybody got used to.
但是我幽默地消除了家人的嘲讽和魔力，很快每个人都习惯了。
wane: v.   逐渐变小，变弱
The idea, however, my enthusiasm waned, the time I spend at exercises gradually diminished.
但是，我的热情逐渐减弱，我在锻炼上花费的时间逐渐减少。
Little by little the 11 minutes fell to zero. By January 10th, I was back to where I had started from.
11分钟逐渐降至零。到1月10日，我回到了我开始的地方。
I argued that if I spent less time exhausting myself at exercises in the morning,
我认为，如果我早上花更少的时间在锻炼中疲惫不堪，
I would keep my mind fresh for reading when I got home formwork resisting the hypnotizing effect of
当我回到家的模板上，我会全心全意阅读，以抵抗的催眠效果
television. I sat in my room for a few evenings with my eyes glued to book. One night, however,
电视。我坐在房间里度过了几个晚上，我的眼睛粘着预订。但是，有一天晚上
feeling cold and lonely, I went downstairs and sat in front of the television pretending to read.
我感到寒冷和孤独，我下楼，坐在电视前，假装读书。
undoing: n.   祸根，毁灭的原因
That proved to be my undoing. For I soon got back to my old bad habit of dozing off in front of the
事实证明这是我的失败。因为我很快回到了我的旧坏习惯
screen: n.   电视机屏幕
screen. I still haven't given up my resolution to do more reading. In fact, I have just bought a book
屏幕。我仍然没有放弃我的决议来进行更多阅读。实际上，我刚买了一本书
entitled How to Read a Thousand Words a Minute. Perhaps it will solve my problem, but I just haven't
题为“如何阅读一千个单词”。也许它会解决我的问题，但我只是没有
had time to read it.
有时间阅读它。